Alan W. Steelman papers, Inclusive: 1960-2003, Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Alan W. Steelman papers
Inclusive: 1960-2003, Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
90
Alan W. Steelman, 1942 -
195 document boxes and 3 oversized flat boxes (16 inch width).
The Alan Steelman papers chronicle the U.S. congressional tenure of Alan Steelman, encompassing the years 1973-1976. Additionally, the papers contain campaign materials, a biographical section spanning 1960-2003, press releases, correspondence, and audio-visual items, among other materials.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Alan Steelman (1942- ) represented Texas's Fifth District from 1973-1976 in the U.S. House of Representatives as a Republican. He ran a distinctive "walking campaign" against incumbent Democrat Earle Cabell and won. At the date of his election, Nov. 7, 1972, Steelman was the youngest Republican member of the House at age 29 and earned a post-graduate fellowship at Harvard's Institute for Politics in late 1972. Steelman's Congressional career immediately blossomed. He was named one of TIME Magazine's "200 Emerging Young National Leaders" in 1974. While in Congress, Steelman served on two committeesDLGovernment Operations and Interior and Insular Affairs. Environmental issues were one area in which Steelman left his mark, particularly the fight against the Trinity River Canal and for the formation of Big Thicket National Preserve. Other legislative priorities for Steelman included energy, transportation, veterans, wage and price controls, and Social Security.
His road to the House began with his upbringing in two towns in Arkansas: Arkadelphia and Fordyce. Steelman later attended Baylor University on a baseball scholarship and received his B.A. in Political Science in 1964. Next, he led the Republican Party of Dallas County from January 1966 to January 1969, and in 1971 graduated from Southern Methodist University with an M.L.A. During his leadership of the Dallas County Republicans, Steelman also remained executive director of the Sam Wyly Foundation of Dallas from January to September in 1969. President Richard Nixon appointed Steelman the executive director of the President's Advisory Council on Minority Business Enterprise in that same September in 1969. Steelman held that post until he stepped down to run for Congress January 1972.
Steelman ran for the U.S. Senate as a Republican in 1976 and lost to Democratic incumbent Lloyd Bentsen. In 1977, he began work with the Alexander Proudfoot Company, a worldwide consulting firm listed on the London Stock Exchange. He was appointed by Governor George W. Bush to the Texas Growth Fund Board, a $600 million venture capital fund run by the State of Texas. Other posts included Vice Chairman of the Board at the John Tower Center for Political Studies at SMU and the Trinity Foundation, Chairman of the Dallas Council on World Affairs, and former President of Maxager Technology, Inc. (now Profit Velocity Solutions), a private, California-based, software company.
While at Proudfoot, Steelman was Group President for the Asia-Pacific region. This enabled him to live in Singapore for eight years and build the Proudfoot start-up in that geographical area. Steelman oversaw the company's business interests in Malaysia, New Zealand, Australia, Indonesia, China, Korea, Taiwan, Japan, Hong Kong, and Thailand. He currently lectures on U.S.-Asia relations, drawing from his business experience in that part of the world.
Steelman is married to his wife Susan, the former Susan Seligman Fuller, and is father to five children: Robin Whitehead, Kim Cuban, Allison Carter, Alan Steelman Jr., and Alex Steelman. He has two stepchildren, Daniel Fuller and Elizabeth Fuller.
Scope and Content
The Alan W. Steelman papers contain materials from 1960-2003, the bulk of which are from 1973-1976: Steelman's service as U.S. Representative of Texas's Fifth Congressional District. The Administrative series consists of GOP office and district information, requests, and schedules. The Biographical section has background information on Steelman after his House race victory in 1973 and personal, family news articles from 1960-1969, and a folder of information on his Proudfoot leadership role. Campaigns feature news clippings, press releases, and campaign literature from two years: Steelman's 1972 House Campaign and his 1976 Senate Campaign. A large portion of the news clippings on the Senate campaign have now been rehoused in archival safe folders.
Constituent correspondence are arranged alphabetically, by incoming/outgoing correspondence, and topically.
The Departments and Agencies series enumerates Steelman's contact with numerous federal agencies from 1973-1976. By far, the bulk of this series illuminates how Steelman voiced a variety of constituent concerns to the U.S. Postal Service. Also of note are recommendations written by Steelman on behalf of constituents to different federal departments such as the Department of Labor, Department of Justice, and the White House. The District series for Dallas highlights Dallas area concerns and contains photographs in the file on the Urban Park Baptist Singers. A Texas subseries of the District series mainly consists of materials on individual cities in Steelman's district, but also holds numerous folders on general affairs in Texas or local communities.
Next, Legislation by Committee encompasses bills from ten different Congressional committees. Legislation on banking and currency issues make up the largest subseries, followed by the Judiciary Committee subseries. The Judiciary Committee subseries chronicles sentiment in Steelman's district for and against bills on President Nixon's impeachment and the Watergate break in. Other notable subseries include: Government Operations, Interior & Insular Affairs (both of which Steelman served on) and the Cabinet Committee on Spanish Speaking People. Land use controversies dominates the subseries on Interior and Insular Affairs, just as revenue sharing does in the Government Operations subseries.
The Legislative series contains three subseries. Major topics in the 93rd Congress subseries include, ecology, the economy, commerce, Citizens Band radios, transportation, and FDA consumer vitamin labeling. Land use, conservation, the EPA, ecology, healthcare, transportation, and veterans issues prevail in the 94th Congress series. The Topical subseries in the Legislative series itemizes some of Steelman's highest legislative priorities: AMTRAK, Big Thicket, Energy, and the Trinity River. Binders also held these materials prior to processing. Here, General materials contain legislative analysis from the American Enterprise Institute dated 1965-1967, and later from 1973-1976.
The Columns, Magazines, and Newsletters subseries of the Press are in poor condition. The Magazines subseries highlights Steelman's favorable reception by the mainstream Texas and American media upon his election and after his two terms in Congress. Steelman's Speeches and Floor Statements are in average condition and range from 1968 to his years after Congress. All of the post-Congressional speeches are undated and the majority of the speeches are from 1973. Additionally, most of the speeches were written on a typewriter with hand-written corrections. The Voting Record series retains alpha ordering by issue from the years 1973 to 1975. Steelman's voting by issue in 1976 is missing, but his roll call votes from 1973 to1976 exist in this series. The Photographs in the Audio-Visual series largely came out of three notebooks. A little over half of the photographs are undated and many have negatives. A list of the monthly radio programs Steelman gave in the Reel-to-Reel items.
The Clippings series contains photocopied clippings and is in good condition. This series spans the years 1966-2002 and has four subseries: General, House Campaign, News Clippings Scrapbooks, and Senate Campaign. The General subseries consists of articles from Steelman's time as chair of the Dallas County Republican Party and the Dallas Council on World Affairs to his directorship of the Wyly Foundation and employment at the Alexander Proudfoot Company. The News Clippings Scrapbooks encompass the years 1973 to 1976 and are oversized. Lastly, the Casework series ranges from 1975 to 1976.
Arrangement
The Alan W. Steelman papers are arranged in 14 series by format and alphabetically according to series title, with alphabetical ordering within those series. The series are: I. Administrative, II. Biographical, III. Campaigns, IV. Correspondence, V. Departments and Agencies, VI. District, VII. Legislation by Committee, VIII. Legislative, IX. Press, X. Speeches and Floor Statements, XI. Voting Record, XII. Audio-Visual, XIII. Clippings, XIV. Casework.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to W.R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 90. Acquired 1977-01-01
Related Resources
Related references
"Steelman, Alan Watson.” Biographical Directory of the United States Congress. Accessed June 18, 2015.
Alan Steelman papers, Accession #90, Baylor Collections of Political Materials, W. R. Poage Legislative Library, Baylor University.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Steelman, Alan -- Archives.; Steelman, Alan.
Subjects (Organizations)
Amtrak.; United States Postal Service -- Records and correspondence.; United States. Congress. House -- Records and correspondence.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs -- Records and correspondence.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on the Judiciary -- Records and correspondence.; United States. Congress. House.; United States. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare -- Records and correspondence.; United States. Department of Housing and Urban Development -- Records and correspondence.
Places
Big Thicket National Preserve (Tex.); Trinity River (Tex.); United States -- Politics and government -- 1974-1977.
Subjects
Banking law -- United States.; Environmental law -- United States.; Legislators -- United States -- Archives.; Legislators -- United States.; Money -- Law and legislation -- United States.; Newsletters.; Political campaigns -- Texas.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Legislative materials.; Photographs.; Records (Documents); Speeches.
- Administrative, 1973-1976; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series encompasses Steelman's administrative documents from his entire time in public office, 1973 to 1976. It includes: General Office Files, Requests, and Schedules. General office files contains information on Steelman's ratings, press releases, public relations, and his application for the Outstanding Young Man award. Constituent requests reside in Requests. Schedules include Steelman's district and D.C. schedules as well as his wife's schedule from 1973. This series is in good condition.
  - General Office Files, 1973-1976; 1
    - Steelman’s Official Biographies, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Assorted Biographical Forms, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bills Paid, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Card Acknowledgements (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Card Acknowledgements (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Card Acknowledgements (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Citizenship Letters, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Compliments, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Constituent, Public Relations, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - D.C./Dallas Campaign Releases, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Contract Notifications, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Grants, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Gridiron Program, Dallas Press Club, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Income Disclosures, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Information on Fifth District, 1973, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Information Packet, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Invitations Accepted, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Media Information Sheets, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Outstanding Young Man Application, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Postal patron mailings, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Press Calendar List, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Ratings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ratings, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Republican Congressional Committee, PR Account, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Republican Congressional Committee, PR Account, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - State GOP Party Letters, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Thank You Letters (1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Thank You Letters (2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Thank You Letters (3 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Tom Lankford Bills, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Voting Record, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Voting Record Index (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Voting Record Index (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Requests, 1974-1976; 2
    - Autographed Photographs, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - General, October 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - General (1 of 2), 1975 January-March (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - General (2 of 2), 1975 January-March (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - General (1 of 3), 1975 April-September (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General (2 of 3), 1975 April-September (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General (3 of 3), 1975 April-September (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - General (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - General (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - General (1 of 5), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - General (2 of 5), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - General (3 of 5), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - General (4 of 5), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - General (5 of 5), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Request Information, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, 1973-1976; 3
    - Carolyn Steelman’s Schedules, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - District (1 of 6), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - District (2 of 6), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - District (3 of 6), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - District (4 of 6), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - District (5 of 6), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - District (6 of 6), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - District (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - District (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - District (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - District (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - District, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Originals & Backup Information (1 of 2), 1973 January (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Originals & Backup Information (2 of 2), 1973 January (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Originals & Backup Information, 1973 April (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Originals & Backup Information, 1973 May (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Originals & Backup Information, 1973 June-July (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Originals & Backup Information, 1973 August-September (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Originals & Backup Information (1 of 3), 1973 October-December (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Originals & Backup Information (2 of 3), 1973 October-December (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Originals & Backup Information (3 of 3), 1973 October-December (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Originals (1 of 5), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Originals (2 of 5), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Originals (3 of 5), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Originals (4 of 5), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Originals (5 of 5), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Originals (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Originals (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Originals (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Originals, Washington (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Originals, Washington (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Originals, Washington (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Out of State, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Statewide Events, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Biographical, 1960-2003; 2
  General condition: Average.
  This series includes documents on Steelman's personal life from the years 1960-2003. It has folders delineating his involvement with the Dallas Council on World Affairs, his Proudfoot company profile, news clippings from 1972 on his uncle, John R. Steelman, an aide to President Harry Truman, and tickets to 2003 Texas Rangers games. This series is in average condition.
  - General, 1973-2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Dallas Council on World Affairs, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Personal/Family News Articles, General, 1960-1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Personal/Family News Articles, John R. Steelman, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Proudfoot Management Profile, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Campaigns, 1972; 1976, undated; 3
  This series holds two features: U.S. House and U.S. Senate materials. The U.S. House materials contain campaign items, a booklet, news clippings, and envelopes. The U.S. Senate campaign materials contain news clippings on Republican primary opponents, brochures, press releases, small banners, and a "Steelman for Senate" campaign button and bumper sticker, among other items. Most of the news clippings are copies. This series is in good condition.
  - U.S. House, 1972, undated; 1
    - US House, Booklet, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - US House, Envelopes, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - US House, News Clips, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - US House, Students for Steelman, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Senate, 1976, undated; 2
    - US Senate, Brochures, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - US Senate, Capitol Press Corps, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - US Senate, Fundraiser, 1976 June 9 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - US Senate, News Clips, Dallas Morning News, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - US Senate, News Clips, Dallas Times Herald, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - US Senate, News Clips, Assorted District, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - US Senate, News Clips, Out-of-District, A-F, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - US Senate, News Clips, Out-of-District, G-Z, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - US Senate, Opposition, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - US Senate, Opposition, 1975 December (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - US Senate, Press Releases, 1976 March (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - US Senate, Press Releases, 1976 April - May (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - US Senate, Press Releases, 1976 June - July (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - US Senate, Press Releases, 1976 August (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - US Senate, Press Releases, 1976 September (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - US Senate, Press Releases, 1976 October (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - US Senate, Promotional Materials, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - US Senate, Questionnaire Response, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - US Senate, TX GOP Women’s Club List, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - US Senate, TX TV Stations, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1972-1976, undated; 4
  This series comprises the majority of Steelman's correspondence with constituents in four subseries by year: 1972-1973, 1974, 1975, 1976. Each subseries except the 1976 subseries contains four sub-subseries: Alpha, Incoming, Outgoing, and Topical. Incoming and Outgoing sub-subseries deal with praise, thanks, and congratulations to and from Steelman. The topical sections have letters on pertinent issues from that year, such as Steelman's controversial 1973 naming of the federal building in Dallas after his opponent in the 1973 Texas Fifth Congressional District race, Earle Cabell. This series is in good condition. Alphabetical ordering by the first two letters of the constituent's last name structures the 1973 correspondence. Incoming and outgoing correspondence for 1972-1973 mainly consists of thank you notes, praise, and congratulatory letters while the 1972-1973 topical subseries heavily leans towards Dallas Metroplex issues. The years of 1974-1976 mirror the 1972-1973 arrangement and thematic focus. 1976 correspondence lacks an alpha subseries.
  - 1972-1973, undated; 1
    - Alpha, 1972-1973; 1
      - Aa-Al, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Am-Az, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Ba, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Be-Blv, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Bo-Brink, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Brinl-Bz, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Ca, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Ce-Cl, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Co, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Cr-Cz, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Da-De, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Df-Dz, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - E, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Fa-Fl, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Fo-Fz, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Ga-Gn, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Go-Gz, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Ha, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - He-Hi, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Ho-Hz, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - I, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Ja-Ji, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Jo-Jz, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Ka-Kh, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Ki-Kz, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - La-Le, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Li-Lz, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Ma, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Mc, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Me-Mi, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Mo-Mz, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - N, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - O, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Pa-Ph, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Pi-Pu, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Q, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Ra-Ri, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Ro-Ry, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Sa-Se, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Sf-Sl, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Sm-So, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Sp-Sz (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Sp-Sz (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Ta-Th, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - U, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - V, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Wa, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - We, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Wh, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Wi (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Wi (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Wo-Wy, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - XYZ, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Incoming, 1972-1973, undated; 2
      - General, 1972-1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - General, 1973 May- July (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - General, 1973 May- July (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Praise and Thanks (1 of 2), 1972 November (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Praise and Thanks (2 of 2), 1972 November (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Praise and Thanks, 1972-1973 December-January (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Praise and Thanks, 1973 February-April (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing, 1972-1973; 3
      - General (1 of 2), 1973 January-April (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - General (2 of 2), 1973 January-April (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - General, 1973 May-June (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Thanks and Congratulations (1 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Thanks and Congratulations (2 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Thanks and Congratulations (3 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Thanks and Congratulations (4 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Thanks and Congratulations (5 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Topical, 1972-1973; 4
      - American Indian Center of Dallas, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Cabell Federal Building, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Crackpots, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)